So, another AI tool that we want to talk about and we want to go through,
especially when it comes to AI chatbots and especially when it comes to text-based artificial
intelligence tools, this one is hyper-right, right? So, I searched the name on Google, hyper-right,
and what hyper-right provides us with is basically writing assistants, right? So,
just like plenty of other options that we have included in this very course that we're in,
hyper-right is also another writing assistant and can help us a lot when it comes to writing in
general, right? So, I open on the first result, which is referring me to hyper-rightai.com,
and as you see, we have AI tools, so if I click on it, it will probably take me to the introduction
of it. So, we have a summarizer, we have rewrite content, we have AI writer,
AI book reviewer, free AI summarizer, we have a lot of tools over here, right?